A Guide to the Russell Sage Foundation records, Publications FA086
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Monographs, Bulletins, and Books Index, 1908-1975; 1; 1.33 Cubic Feet 100 35mm microfilm reels; 100 Reels 100 microfilm reels (35mm)
  - Weinstein, Eugene A. - The Self-image of the Foster Child, 1960 (Reel 66)
  - Goldmark, Pauline (ed.) - Boyhood and Lawlessness (West Side Studies), 1912 (Reel 66)
  - True, Ruth S. - The Neglected Girl (West Side Studies), 1914 (Reel 66)
  - Cartwright, Otho G. - The Middle West Side (West Side Studies), 1914 (Reel 66)
  - Anthony, Katharine - Mothers Who Must Earn (West Side Studies), 1914 (Reel 66)
  - Wheeler, Stanton (ed.) - On Record - Files and Dossiers in American Life, 1969 (Reel 66)
  - Wieck, Edward, A. - The American Miners' Association, 1940 (Reel 67)
  - Wieck, Edward, A. - Preventing Fatal Explosions in Coal Mines, 1942 (Reel 67)
  - Wilensky, Harold L. - Industrial Society and Social Welfare, 1965 (Reel 67)
  - Witmer, Helen Leland - Independent Adoptions, 1963 (Reel 67)
  - Woods, Robert A. - Handbook of Settlements, 1911 (Reel 68)
  - Woods, Robert A. - The Settlement Horizon, 1922 (Reel 68)
  - Young, Donald Ramsey - Trusteeship and the Management of Foundations, 1969 (Reel 68)
  - Yu, Frederick T. C. et al. - Conference on Behavioral Sciences and the Mass Media, 1966 (Reel 68)
  - Zurcher, Arnold J. et al. - The Foundation Administrator - A study of those who manage America's foundations, 1972 (Reel 68)
  - Raby, R. Cornelius - The Regulation of Pawnbroking, 1924 (Reel 69)
  - Raby, R. Cornelius - Effective Use of Social Science Research in the Federal Services, 1950 (Reel 69)
  - Raby, R. Cornelius - Report of the Princeton Conference of the History of Philanthropy, in the United States, 1956 (Reel 69)
  - Raby, R. Cornelius - A Statistical Program for the Department of Health of the City of New York, 1956 (Reel 69)
  - Wheeler, Stanton - Juvenile Delinquency - Its Prevention and Control, 1966 (Reel 69)
  - Glass, David C. - Neurophysiology and Emotion. Proceedings of a Conference under Auspices of Russell Sage Foundation and the Rockefeller University, 1967 (Reel 70)
  - Glass, David C. - Genetics. Proceedings of a Conference under the Auspices of Russell Sage Foundation, Social Science Research Council, and the Rockefeller University, 1968 (Reel 70)
  - Glass, David C. - Environmental Influences. Proceedings of a Conference under the Auspices of the Russell Sage Foundation and Rockefeller University, 1968 (Reel 70)
  - Nelson, Ralph L. - Economic Factors in the Growth of Corporation Giving, 1970 (Reel 71)
  - Bassett, Edward M. - The Master Plan. With a Discussion of the Theory of Community and Planning Legislation, 1938 (Reel 72)
  - Bassett, Edward M. - Zoning, 1936 (Reel 72)
  - Bassett, Edward M. - Zoning, reprinted with additions, 1940 (Reel 72)
  - Carlin, Jerome Edward - Civil Justice and the Poor. Issues for Sociological Research, 1966 (Reel 73)
  - The Foundation Directory, Second Edition (Reel 74)
  - The Foundation Directory, Third Edition (Reel 75)
  - Janowitz, Morris - Sociology and the Military Establishment, 1959 (Reel 76)
  - Janowitz, Morris - Sociology and the Military Establishment, Revised Edition, 1965 (Reel 76)
  - Janowitz, Morris - Sociology and the Military Establishment, Revised Edition, 1969 (Reel 76)
  - Jordan, Wilbur K. - The Charities of London, 1480-1660, 1961 (Reel 76)
  - Jordan, Wilbur K. - The Charities of Rural England, 1480-1660, 1961 (Reel 76)
  - Jordan, Wilbur K. - Philanthropy in England, 1480-1660, 1960 (Reel 76)
  - G.A.F. (Ed.) - Directory of European Foundations, 1969 (Reel 77)
  - Charity Organization Department, Publications Nos. 1-35 (Reel 78)
  - Charity Organization Department, Publications Nos. 36-72 (Reel 78)
  - Charity Organization Department, Publications Nos. 73-81 (Reel 79)
  - Department of Child Helping, Publications Nos. 1-15 (Reel 79)
  - Department of Child Helping, Publications Nos. 16-30 (Reel 80)
  - Department of Child Helping, Publications Nos. 31-52 (Reel 80)
  - Department of Child Hygiene, Publications Nos. 1-50 (Reel 81)
  - Department of Child Hygiene, Publications Nos. 51-85 (Reel 81)
  - Department of Child Hygiene, Publications Nos. 86-110 (Reel 82)
  - Department of Child Hygiene, Publications Nos. 111-134 (Reel 82)
  - Consumer Credit Studies Department, Publication No. 1 (Reel 82)
  - Department of Delinquency and Penology, Publications Nos. 1-3 (Reel 82)
  - Department of Education, Publications Nos. 135-143 (Reel 83)
  - Department of Industrial Studies, Publications Nos. 1-7 (Reel 84)
  - Department of Industrial Studies, Publications Nos. 8-9 (Reel 84)
  - Library Bulletins, Nos. 1-25 (Reel 84)
  - Library Bulletins, Nos. 26-50 (Reel 84)
  - Library Bulletins, Nos. 51-75 (Reel 84)
  - Library Bulletins, Nos. 76-100 (Reel 85)
  - Library Bulletins, Nos. 101-125 (Reel 85)
  - Library Bulletins, Nos. 126-150 (Reel 85)
  - Library Bulletins, Nos. 151-158 (Reel 85)
  - Library Bulletins, Nos. 159-163 (Reel 85)
  - Library Publications, 1-4 (Reel 85)
  - Library Bibliographies, 1-5 (Reel 85)
  - Prevention of Blindness Committee, Bulletin Nos. 1 and 2 (Reel 85)
  - Department of Recreation, Publications, Nos. R and Rec (Reel 85)
  - Department of Recreation, Publications, Nos. 135-145 (Reel 85)
  - Department of Recreation, Publications, Nos. 146-159 (Reel 86)
  - Division of Remedial Loans, Publications Nos. 1-12 (Reel 86)
  - Division of Remedial Loans, Publications Nos. 13-26 (Reel 87)
  - Division of Remedial Loans, Publications Nos. 27-46 (Reel 87)
  - Southern Highland Division, Publications Nos. 1-3 (Reel 87)
  - Department of Statistics, Publications 1-10 (Reel 88)
  - Department of Statistics, Publications 11-20 (Reel 88)
  - Department of Surveys and Exhibits, Publications Nos. 1-16 (Reel 88)
  - Department of Surveys and Exhibits, Publications Nos. 17-30 (Reel 89)
  - Department of Surveys and Exhibits, Publications Nos. 31-32 (Reel 89)
  - Supplement to Publicity Methods Reading List, No. 31 (Reel 89)
  - Annual Reports, 1947-1948 through 1951-1952, 1947-1952 (Reel 90)
  - Annual Reports, 1952-1953 through 1956-1957, 1952-1957 (Reel 90)
  - Annual Reports, 1957-1958 through 1961-1962, 1957-1962 (Reel 90)
  - Annual Report, 1962-1963 (Reel 90)
  - Annual Report, 1963-1964 (Reel 90)
  - Annual Report, 1964-1965 (Reel 90)
  - Annual Report, 1965-1966 (Reel 90)
  - Annual Report, 1966-1967 (Reel 90)
  - Annual Report, 1967-1968 (Reel 90)
  - Annual Report, 1968-1969 (Reel 90)
  - Annual Report, 1969-1970 (Reel 91)
  - Annual Report, 1970-1971 (Reel 91)
  - Annual Report, 1971-1972 (Reel 91)
  - Annual Report, 1972-1973 (Reel 91)
  - Catalouges, 1913-1919 (Reel 92)
  - Catalouges, 1918-1927 (Reel 92)
  - Catalouges, 1928-1933 (Reel 92)
  - Catalouges, 1934-1939 (Reel 93)
  - Catalouges, 1940-1946 (Reel 93)
  - Catalouges, 1947-1955 (Reel 93)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, May 1932, 1932 May (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, June 1932, 1932 June (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, November 1932, 1932 November (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, January 1933, 1933 January (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, April 1933, 1933 April (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, July 1933, 1933 July (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, November 1933, 1933 November (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, January 1934, 1934 January (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, April 1934, 1934 April (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, July 1934, 1934 July (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, November 1934, 1934 November (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, January 1935, 1935 January (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, April 1935, 1935 April (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, July 1935, 1935 July (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, October 1935, 1935 October (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, January 1936, 1936 January (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, April 1936, 1936 April (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, July 1936, 1936 July (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, October 1936, 1936 October (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, January 1937, 1937 January (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, April 1937, 1937 April (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, July 1937, 1937 July (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, October 1937, 1937 October (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, January 1938, 1938 January (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, April 1938, 1938 April (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, July 1938, 1938 July (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, October 1938, 1938 October (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, March 1939, 1939 March (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, June 1939, 1939 June (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, September 1939, 1939 September (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, December 1939, 1939 December (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, March 1940, 1940 March (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, June 1940, 1940 June (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, September 1940, 1940 September (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, December 1940, 1940 December (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, March 1941, 1941 March (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, June 1941, 1941 June (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, September 1941, 1941 September (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, December 1941, 1941 December (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, March 1942, 1942 March (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, June 1942, 1942 June (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, September 1942, 1942 September (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, December 1942, 1942 December (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, March 1943, 1943 March (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, June 1943, 1943 June (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, September 1943, 1943 September (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, December 1943, 1943 December (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, March 1944, 1944 March (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, June 1944, 1944 June (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, September 1944, 1944 September (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, December 1944, 1944 December (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, March 1945, 1945 March (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, June 1945, 1945 June (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, September 1945, 1945 September (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, December 1945, 1945 December (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, March 1946, 1946 March (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, June 1946, 1946 June (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, September 1946, 1946 September (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, December 1946, 1946 December (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, March 1947, 1947 March (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, June 1947, 1947 June (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, September 1947, 1947 September (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, December 1947, 1947 December (Reel 94)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Bulletin, March 1948, 1948 March (Reel 94)
  - Acton, Amy Florence - Local Option in Massachusetts, 1911 (Reel 95)
  - Goldmark, Pauline - Women and Children in the Canning Industry - An Investigation in New York State, 1908 (Reel 95)
  - Charity Organization Bulletin, Vol. I-II (Reel 96)
  - Charity Organization Bulletin, Vol. III (Reel 96)
  - Charity Organization Bulletin, Vol. IV (Reel 96)
  - Charity Organization Bulletin, Vol. V (Reel 96)
  - Charity Organization Bulletin, Vol. VI (Reel 96)
  - Charity Organization Bulletin, Vol. VII (Reel 96)
  - Charity Organization Bulletin, Vol. VIII (Reel 97)
  - Charity Organization Bulletin, Vol. IX (Reel 97)
  - Social Case History, Series II (Reel 97)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Confidential Bulletin, No. 1 (Reel 98)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Reel 99)
  - Land, Kenneth C. (Ed.) - Social Indicator Models, 1975 (Reel 99)
  - Phelps, Edmund S. - Altruism, Morality, and Economic Theory, 1975 (Reel 99)
  - Bernstein, Ilene Nagel - Academic and Entrepreneurial Research - The Consequences of Diversity in Federal Evaluation Studies, 1975 (Reel 99)
  - French, David G. - Working Communally - Patterns and Possibilities, 1975 (Reel 99)
  - Friedman, Lawrence M. - The Legal System - a social science perspective, 1975 (Reel 99)
  - Crane, Diane - The Sanctity of Social Life - Physicians' Treatment of Critically-ill Patients, 1975 (Reel 99)
  - Cook, Thomas D. et al. - Sesame Street Revisited, 1975 (Reel 100)
  - Hauser, Philip Morris - Social Statistics in Use, 1975 (Reel 100)
  - Katz, Jay - Catostrophic Diseases - Who Decides What, 1975 (Reel 100)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Reel 100)